(Howard(entering):)All right, we got a problem.
(Leonard:)What's up?
(Howard:)The Air Force contacted me
about our quantum gyroscope.
(Howard:)They want to have
a meeting.
(Leonard:)Really?
(Raj:)Yeah. This military guy
showed up at Howard's door.
(Raj:)He was terrifying.
(Sheldon:)Oh, what did he say?
(Raj:)He gave me his business card
(Raj:)and asked me to please
pass it along to Howard.
(Sheldon:)That doesn't sound terrifying.
(Raj:)To a white guy born here, no.
(Raj:)If you are a brown guy
whose name has
(Raj:)a lot of syllables in it--
terrifying.
(Leonard:)You realize if the military declares our
research classified,
(Leonard:)they can take the whole
thing away from us.
(Howard:)And if that happens,
(Howard:)we'll never be able
to sell it commercially.
(Leonard:)There goes our big payday.
I was counting
(Howard:)on that money-- I need
to make as much as my wife
(Howard:)so I don't have
to try so hard in bed.
(Leonard:)You do that, too?
(Howard:)Oh, yeah. How do you think
I stay this thin?
(Sheldon:)Gentlemen, I think we are
losing sight of the real issue.
(Sheldon:)We are on the precipice
of becoming faceless cogs
(Sheldon:)in the military-industrial
complex.
(Sheldon:)Isn't that exciting?
(Raj:)You're kidding, right?
Not at all. In Star Wars,
when the stormtroopers
(Sheldon:)would march
in perfect formation,
(Sheldon:)harassing civilians,
didn't you ever think,
"Hey, that could be me"?
(Howard:)Sheldon,
we could be contributing
(Howard:)to a weapons system
that oppresses mankind
(Howard:)for the next thousand years.
(Sheldon:)Okay, Howard's on board.
What do you think, Leonard?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪